Foster Gunnison, Jr. Papers
© 2006 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Morris Kight Papers, 1969-1973
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1969-1973
    - Angela Douglas to Kight, 1970 (Box 56:, Folder 647)
    - Craig Hanson to Kight, 1970-1971 (Box 56:, Folder 648)
    - Kight to Gunnison, 1970-1973 (Box 56:, Folder 649)
  - Subseries B: Organizations, 1970-1971
    - Christopher Street West, 1970-1971 (Box 56:, Folder 650)
    - Gay Liberation Front, Los Angeles, Administrative and Office Files, 1970-1971 (Box 56:, Folder 651)
    - Gay Liberation Front, Los Angeles, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 56:, Folder 652)
    - Gay Liberation Front, Los Angeles, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 56:, Folder 653)
    - Gay Liberation Front, Los Angeles, Fliers, 1970-1971 (Box 56:, Folder 654)
    - Metropolitan Community Church of Los Angeles, 1970 (Box 57:, Folder 655)
    - Metropolitan Community Church of Miami, 1970 (Box 57:, Folder 656)
    - Psychedelic Venus Church, 1970-1971 (Box 57:, Folder 657)
    - Society of David, 1970-1971 (Box 57:, Folder 658)
    - Ephemera and Stickers, 1970 (Box 57:, Folder 659)
    - Fliers, 1970 (Box 57:, Folder 660)
    - Manifestos and Political Platforms, 1970 (Box 57:, Folder 661)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 57:, Folder 662)
    - Adult books, films and novelties - mailers, 1970 (Box 57:, Folder 663)
- Series VI: Society for the Preservation and Encouragement of Barber Shop Quartet Singing in America (SPEBSQSA), undated, 1945, 1956-1993
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1965-1993
    - to/from Gunnison, 1965-1977 (Box 69:, Folder 951)
    - to/from Gunnison, 1978-1979 (Box 69:, Folder 952)
    - to/from Gunnison, 1980-1993 (Box 69:, Folder 953)
    - to/from SPEBSQSA (Hartford Chapter), 1965-1979 (Box 69:, Folder 954)
    - to/from SPEBSQSA (Hartford Chapter), 1980-1992 (Box 69:, Folder 955)
    - to/from Board of Directors of SPEBSQSA (Hartford Chapter), 1970-1992 (Box 69:, Folder 956)
  - Subseries B: Administrative Records, undated, 1945, 1956-1993
    - Account Records, 1978-1979, 1990-1991 (Box 69:, Folder 957)
    - Attendance Records, 1971, 1973 (Box 69:, Folder 958)
    - Bank Account, Blank Forms, undated (Box 70:, Folder 959)
    - Bank Account, Books, undated (Box 70:, Folder 960)
    - Bank Account, Records, 1975 (Box 70:, Folder 961)
    - Bank Account, Records, 1977 (Box 70:, Folder 962)
    - Bank Account, Records, 1977 (Box 70:, Folder 962)
    - Bank Account, Records, 1978 (Box 70:, Folder 964)
    - Bank Account, Records, 1978 (Box 70:, Folder 965)
    - Bank Account, Records, 1978, 1979, 1981 (Box 70:, Folder 966)
    - Bills, 1966-1969 (Box 70:, Folder 967)
    - Bills, 1971-1978 (Box 71:, Folder 968)
    - Bills, 1978-1993 (Box 71:, Folder 969)
    - Blank and Mockup Forms, undated (Box 71:, Folder 970)
    - Brochures, undated, 1971, 1976 (Box 71:, Folder 971)
    - Budget and Expense Records, 1970-1985 (Box 71:, Folder 972)
    - Bulletin, Hartford Harmony, 1959 (Box 71:, Folder 973)
    - Bulletin, Harmony, 1973-1975 (Box 71:, Folder 974)
    - Bulletin, The Insurance City Chorus, 1975 (Box 71:, Folder 975)
    - Bylaws, Constitutions, Ethics, 1956-1973 (Box 71:, Folder 976)
    - Cash Receipt Records, Afterglow Sales Reports, 1967, 1981 (Box 71:, Folder 977)
    - Catalogues, Barbershopper's Shop, 1985-1991 (Box 71:, Folder 978)
    - Certificate of Recognition from Mayor, 1975 (Box 78:, Folder 1049)
    - Certificates, 1945, 1956 (Box 71:, Folder 979)
    - Chapter Improvement Committee, 1987 (Box 71:, Folder 980)
    - Concert Programs, 1963, 1965 (Box 71:, Folder 981)
    - Concert Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 71:, Folder 982)
    - Directory of Chapters, 1971 (Box 72:, Folder 983)
    - Dues Records, 1977 (Box 72:, Folder 984)
    - Festival of Harmony, 1973-1993 (Box 72:, Folder 985)
    - Festival of Harmony, Financial Statements, 1965-1972 (Box 72:, Folder 986)
    - Festival of Harmony, 1976-1978 (Box 72:, Folder 987)
    - Festival of Harmony, Broadside, 1974 (Box 78:, Folder 1048)
    - Festival of Harmony, Fliers, 1964-1986 (Box 72:, Folder 988)
    - Festival of Harmony, Programs, 1965-1973 (Box 72:, Folder 989)
    - Festival of Harmony, Programs, 1974-1985 (Box 72:, Folder 990)
    - Festival of Harmony, Programs, 1989-1993 (Box 72:, Folder 991)
    - Festival of Harmony, Seating Arrangement, 1966-1978 (Box 73:, Folder 992)
    - Festival of Harmony, Tickets, undated (Box 73:, Folder 993)
    - Festival of Harmony, Tickets, undated (Box 73:, Folder 994)
    - Festival of Harmony, Tickets, undated (Box 73:, Folder 995)
    - Festival of Harmony, Ticket Sales Operating Instructions, undated (Box 73:, Folder 996)
    - Financial Statement, 1978 (Box 78:, Folder 1047)
    - Insurance Certificate, 1978-1990 (Box 73:, Folder 997)
    - Invoices, 1966-1969 (Box 73:, Folder 998)
    - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 73:, Folder 999)
    - Handwritten Notes, 1965-1969 (Box 73:, Folder 1000)
    - Handwritten Notes, 1970-1978 (Box 73:, Folder 1001)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1969-1993 (Box 73:, Folder 1002)
    - Meeting Announcements, 1986-1987 (Box 73:, Folder 1003)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1970 January - April (Box 73:, Folder 1004)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1970 May - December (Box 74:, Folder 1005)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 74:, Folder 1006)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 74:, Folder 1007)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 74:, Folder 1008)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1976 (Box 74:, Folder 1009)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 74:, Folder 1010)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 74:, Folder 1011)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box 75:, Folder 1012)
    - Mailing Lists, 1978-1983 (Box 75:, Folder 1013)
    - Membership, 1960-1991 (Box 75:, Folder 1014)
    - Membership Cards, 1979, 1987 (Box 75:, Folder 1015)
    - Membership Lists, Yearbook, 1981-1983 (Box 75:, Folder 1016)
    - Memos, undated, 1970-1991 (Box 75:, Folder 1017)
    - Music Scores, 1960-1976 (Box 75:, Folder 1018)
    - Music Scores, undated, 1969 (Box 75:, Folder 1019)
    - Music Scores, undated, 1974-1977 (Box 75:, Folder 1020)
    - Music Scores, 1973-1987 (Box 75:, Folder 1021)
    - Newsclippings, 1967-1984 (Box 75:, Folder 1022)
    - Officers, 1970, 1973 (Box 75:, Folder 1023)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 75:, Folder 1024)
    - Printing Proofs of Office Documents, undated (Box 78:, Folder 1045-1046)
    - Sales Records, 1978 (Box 78:, Folder 1044)
    - Sponsor Contracts, 1964 (Box 76:, Folder 1025)
    - Sponsor Contracts, 1965 (Box 76:, Folder 1026)
    - Sponsor Contracts, 1966 (Box 76:, Folder 1027)
    - Sponsor Contracts, undated, 1972-1978 (Box 76:, Folder 1028)
    - Tax Forms, 1967-1986 (Box 76:, Folder 1029)
    - Ticket Sales, 1966 (Box 76:, Folder 1030)
    - Ticket Sales, 1967 (Box 76:, Folder 1031)
    - Ticket Sales, 1968 (Box 76:, Folder 1032)
    - Ticket Sales, 1989 (Box 76:, Folder 1033)
    - Treasurer's Records, 1979-1985 (Box 76:, Folder 1034)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1986-1993 (Box 76:, Folder 1035)
    - Woodshedder Guild, Booklet, undated (Box 77:, Folder 1036)
  - Subseries C: Newsletters, 1969-1993
    - News and Events, Insurance City Chorus, 1969 (Box 77:, Folder 1037)
    - News and Events, Insurance City Chorus, 1970, 1971 (Box 77:, Folder 1038)
    - Policy Notes, Insurance City Chorus, 1976, 1977 (Box 77:, Folder 1039-1040)
    - Policy Notes, 1978-1981, 1985-1993 (Box 77:, Folder 1041-1043)
  - Subseries C: Artifacts, undated, 1967, 1987
    - Buttons and Pins, undated, 1987 (Box 83:, Folder 1052-1058)
    - Honorary Plaque, 1967 (Box 79:)
- Series VII: Photographs, undated, 1958-1993
  - Subseries A: Prints, undated, 196?-1993
    - Celebration of Stonewall Publication, 1993? (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 712)
    - Gunnison, Foster with Bob Martin, 1967 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 713)
    - Gunnison, Foster at a Party, 199-? (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 714)
    - Kalos Banner at Gay Pride March, 197-? (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 715)
    - Kight, Morris, 1970 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 716)
    - Kight, Morris, 1970 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 717)
    - Kight, Morris, 1970 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 718)
    - Kight, Morris, 1970 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 719)
    - Kight, Morris, 1970 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 720)
    - Martin, Bob, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 721)
    - Martin, Bob, Childhood Photographs, 1958-1972 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 722)
    - Martin, Bob, Photographs, 1971 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 723)
    - Perry, Mathew Wedding, 1980 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 724)
    - Perry, Mathew Wedding, 1980 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 725)
    - Rodwell, Craig, Memorial Service, 1993 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 726)
    - Teal, Don, 1971 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 727)
    - Koop, C. Everett, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 736)
    - Gunnison, Foster, 1987 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 737)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1059)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1060)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1061)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1062)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1063)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1064)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1065)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1066)
    - Festival of Harmony, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1067)
    - Barber Quartet Singers, 1984 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1068)
    - Barber Quartet Singers, 1971 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1069)
    - Barber Quartet Singers, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1070)
    - Barber Quartet Singers, undated (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 1071)
  - Subseries B: Slides, 1967-1975
    - Clark, Elizah, 1967 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 728)
    - Kalos, 1971 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 729)
    - Gay Pride March, 1972 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 730)
    - Gay Pride March, 1973, 1975 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 731)
    - New York Pride March, 1971-1975 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 732)
  - Subseries C: Negatives, 1969-1971
    - Photo Masters for ISE Mailing Labels, 1971 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 733)
    - Martin, Bob, Negatives from Childhood, 1969 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 734)
    - NACHO Conference, Negatives, 1969 (Box 1996-0009:, Folder 735)